Hello everyone, in the version of 2024.1, we optimized the function of the sticker code, which can be achieved by directly using the hundred-point pen or unit number to enter the code.
Let's learn how to enter the code through this video.
First of all, we need to ensure that the size is changed to the base code in the object window.
In this file, I will use the middle code M as the base code.
Use the editor code tool to select the heavy sticker.
You can see that there is an extra part of the size in the property editor.
From the menu on the right side, you can choose to use the unit number or hundred-point pen to enter the code.
Use the unit number. You can enter the exact size of each sticker.
Use the hundred-point pen. You can enter the hundred-point number of each sticker.
Because in the industry, when users enter the code for stickers, they usually use hundred-point pen instead of numbers.
This will be more appropriate for users' habit of entering the code for stickers.
So we are here.
Use the hundred-point pen to modify the hundred-point number of the S code and the L code.
You need to pay attention.
Because the base code is M at this time, so the number of M is now unable to be edited.
At this time, if we want to overlap the position of the sticker for the code, we can do it.
You can select the point that needs to be overlapped.
Right-click to select the coordinates that need to be overlapped.
Select X and Y overlapped here.
Switch the code number to check the effect.
Then there is another situation.
How to use the existing code information to enter the code.
It will also be explained in this video.
You can see that there is already a sticker on this board.
The code information is marked with a curve.
At this time, the code only involves the change of location.
The size of the sticker does not change.
First move the sticker to one side.
Then we only need to use the loop outline tool.
Hook this curve.
Then use the edit code tool.
Copy the code of a certain point in this internal shape.
Then select the sticker to paste.
Then move the sticker to the original position.
Finally, see the sticker code information on this board.
You can see that the code of this sticker will have a position and change in size.
First, move the sticker to the side.
Then hook this shape.
Then we need to switch the tool to the edit curve code.
Four points on this internal shape.
Copy once.
Then paste to the four points of the sticker.
Then move the sticker to the original position.
The above is all the content of the sticker code in the shell.
After using the new function.
Everyone will directly put the code in the shell.
Will become more convenient.